in previous tutorials i've gone over a
在以前的教程中，我已经复习了
method of duplicating objects around a
复制对象周围的对象的方法
circle where an object is rotated and
旋转对象所在的圆圈和
stamped in multiple places
在多个地方盖章
this is a really useful technique for
这是一种非常有用的技术
any inkscape user to know and i've had a
任何要认识的Inkscape用户，我都有一个
lot of people ask me how to do something
很多人问我怎么做某事
like this in the past
以前就是这样的
so i feel like this deserves a video of
所以我觉得这值得拍一段视频
its own
它自己的
[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynic.com and in
我是logosbynic.com的尼克
this tutorial i'll be demonstrating how
在本教程中，我将演示
you can stamp an
您可以在一个
object around a circle using inkscape
使用Inkscape环绕圆圈的对象
but before we get started if you'd like
但在我们开始之前，如果你愿意
to learn more about inkscape be sure to
要了解有关Inkscape的更多信息，请务必
check out the inkscape master class it's
查看Inkscape大师类，它是
a collection of over 60 videos where i
60多个视频的集合，其中我
go over
过去
all of the tools and features in
中的所有工具和功能
inkscape and i explain what they are and
Inkscape和我解释了它们是什么
demonstrate how they work
演示它们的工作原理
i'll have a link in the description of
我会在描述中有一个链接
the video if you want to check that out
这个视频如果你想看看的话
so to get us started here on inkscape
为了让我们从Inkscape开始
the first thing we want to do is just
我们要做的第一件事就是
set up the document so that we are all
设置文档，这样我们都可以
working with a similar
使用类似的
layout up here where it says view make
在这里布局，上面写着VIEW Make
sure you have custom selected
确保您已自定义选择
and then come up here to where it says
然后来到这里，上面写着
zoom and zoom in at one to one
以一比一的比例进行放大和放大
and to get us started here as you can
为了让我们尽可能地在这里开始
see i have this example object
看，我有这个示例对象
just for demonstrative purposes you
只是为了说明一下，你
don't have to use this object you can
不必使用此对象，您可以
use whatever object you'd like if you
使用任何您喜欢的对象，如果您
want to follow along you can use a
想要跟上的话可以使用
circle or a star or a letter or whatever
圆圈、星星、字母或其他任何东西
you'd like
你会想要
so if you zoom in on this object over
所以如果你把这个物体放大
here i'm just going to hold ctrl and
在这里，我只需按住Ctrl键并
roll up the mouse wheel to zoom in
卷起鼠标滚轮即可放大
i have this object selected with the
我已使用
select tool and by default it gives us
选择工具，默认情况下它会为我们提供
the scaling handles over here that
这里的鳞片把手
allows us to scale the image
允许我们对图像进行缩放
but if you click on the object again
但如果你再次点击这个物体
you'll get the rotation handles which
你会得到旋转手柄，
allows us to rotate the
允许我们旋转
image or the object around a center
中心周围的图像或物体
point
点
and the center point is located right
并且中心点位于右侧
here it may be difficult for you to see
在这里，您可能很难看到
on my screen but it's this little
在我的屏幕上，但它是这个小
crosshair right here
十字准线就在这里
this represents the axis on which the
这表示在其上
object rotates and you can actually move
物体旋转，你实际上可以移动
that around if you take this and move
如果你拿着这个搬走
this over here to the side
这个放在这边
you'll notice that now the object
您会注意到，现在对象
rotates around
旋转
that that point right there now let me
就在这一点上现在让我
undo that by pressing ctrl z
按Ctrl z可撤消该操作
and you can take this center point and
你可以把这个中心点
move this anywhere you can move this all
把这个搬到任何你能搬得动的地方
the way out here if you want to
离开这里的路，如果你想
and now it'll rotate around that axis
现在它会绕着那个轴旋转
okay so and if at any point if you want
好的，那么，如果你想要的话
to put the rotation center
将旋转中心放在
back in the middle of the object all you
回到物体的中间，所有的你
have to do is hold shift and click on it
要做的就是按住Shift键并单击它
and it'll place it right back in the
它会把它放回原处
middle
中位
so if you wanted to take this object and
所以如果你想把这个物体
duplicate it around a circle
围绕一个圆圈复制它
we can take advantage of this feature
我们可以利用这一功能
right here so let me zoom out a little
就在这里，让我把它放大一点
bit i'm going to hold ctrl and roll down
我要按住Ctrl键然后往下滚
the mouse wheel
鼠标滚轮
i'm going to take this little crosshair
我要拿着这个小十字架
and i'm going to bring this down here
我要把这个带到这里来
but i'm going to hold ctrl so it locks
但我要按住Ctrl键，这样它就会锁定
it onto the vertical axis
把它放到垂直轴上
we want to come straight down like this
我们想像这样直接下来
all the way down here
一路走到这里
now what you can do is you can take this
现在你能做的就是你可以拿着这个
rotation
旋转
handle on the corner here and rotate
把手放在角落里，然后旋转
this around in a circle
这是一个圆圈
and to create duplicate copies of this
并创建此文件的副本
what you can do
你能做什么
is as you're rotating it you can press
当你旋转它的时候，你可以按下
the space bar
空格键
and every time you press the space bar
每次你按下空格键
it'll stamp a copy of it
它会盖上一份复印件
as you see happening on my screen now
就像你现在在我的屏幕上看到的那样
let me go ahead and undo that
让我继续解开它
if you want to take this object and
如果你想把这个物体
rotate it in such a way that you create
以这样的方式旋转它，以便您创建
a symmetrical shape
对称的形状
with each with each individual object
每个对象都有各自的对象
being equally spaced apart
等间距的
what you can do is while you're rotating
你能做的就是在你旋转的时候
hold the ctrl key and it will lock the
按住Ctrl键，它将锁定
rotation onto 15 degree increments
旋转到15度增量
so you can start here go there
所以你可以从这里开始，到那里
there and as you see i am creating a
正如您所看到的，我正在创建一个
symmetrical shape
对称形状
where this object is being stamped
此对象正在被盖章的位置
around a circle
围成一圈
okay so let's say you want to take this
好的，假设你想拿着这个
shape and wrap it around
塑造它并将其包裹起来
a circle that has a predetermined size
具有预定大小的圆
so let me move this out of the way
所以让我把这件事移开
let's create a circle here the circles
让我们在这里创建一个圆圈
and ellipses tool i'm going to click and
和省略号工具，我要点击和
drag hold ctrl to create a perfectly
拖动按住Ctrl键可以创建完美的
round circle
圆的圆
let's say you have a circle like this
假设你有一个这样的圆圈
and let's say
我们可以说
it's sized at let me just change the
它的大小是让我改变一下
size to 200 pixels let's say you want to
大小为200像素，假设您想要
wrap this around a 200 pixel circle
将其环绕200像素的圆圈
what you can do is you can take this
你能做的就是你可以拿着这个
object here let me get rid of these
这里的对象，让我把这些去掉
objects
对象
you can take this object here select it
你可以在这里拿着这个东西，选择它
hold shift click on this object here the
按住Shift键在此处单击此对象
circle
圆
and let's open up the alignment menu
让我们打开对齐菜单
over here where it says align and
在这里，上面写着对齐和
distribute objects
分布对象
and i want to make sure i have last
我想确保我能坚持到最后
selected chosen from this drop down
已从此下拉列表中选择
and where i want to align it is right
我想把它对齐的地方是正确的
here where it says
在这里，它说
align bottom edges of objects to the top
将对象的底部边缘与顶部对齐
edge of the anchor so it's going to
锚的边缘，所以它会
stack it right on top of the circle
把它堆在圆圈的正上方
and then i want to center it up on the
然后我想把它集中在
vertical axis so it's going to put it in
垂直轴，所以它将把它放在
the center
中心
of this object and it's going to put it
它会把它放在
on the top of this object like this
在这个物体的顶部，就像这样
now let me click off of it to deselect
现在，让我单击它以取消选择
everything let me zoom in a little bit
一切都让我放大了一点
so what i want to do is i want to take
所以我想做的是，我想要
this object and wrap it around this
这个对象，并将它包裹在这个
circle
圆
so what i want to do is take the center
所以我想要做的是把中心放在
point or that cross hair for this object
该对象指针或十字线
and place it in the center
把它放在中间
of the circle and the way to do that to
以及如何做到这一点
make sure that it's exactly in the
确保它恰好在
center of the circle what you could do
圆圈中心你能做的事
is you could turn on snapping up here
你可以在这里开启抢购
where it says enable snapping turn that
在它说启用捕捉的地方，转到
on if it's not on already
如果它还没有打开的话就打开
and over here what we're looking for
在这里，我们要找的是
snap centers of objects click on that
对象的捕捉中心单击该按钮
snap and items rotation center we want
我们想要的捕捉和项目旋转中心
to click on that we want to make sure
要点击该选项，我们希望确保
this is the important one right here
这是这里最重要的一个
snap and items rotation center
捕捉和项目旋转中心
this will make it so that when you grab
这将使它在您抓取
that little crosshair it will snap it
那个小小的十字准线会把它折断的
into the center of the object you place
到您放置的对象的中心
it over
一切都结束了
so let me click on this again to get
所以让我再次点击这个来获得
back to the rotation handles and there's
回到旋转手柄，这里有
the center point
中心点
as it already is let me just shift-click
因为它已经存在，所以我只需按住Shift键并单击
that to put that back in the center
把它放回中心
as if we were starting fresh now i'm
就像我们重新开始一样，我现在
going to take this crosshair and i'm
我要拿着这个十字准线，我
going to snap it into the center of the
我要把它拍到中央
circle
圆
and if you notice it automatically snaps
如果你注意到它会自动折断
it right into the center there
它就在那里的中心
and what you can do now is you can
你现在能做的就是
rotate this around you can hold ctrl
旋转它，可以按住Ctrl键
and go through and stamp this
穿过去，盖上这个
and again at each position you just
同样，在每个位置，你只需
press the spacebar and it's stamping it
按下空格键，它就会盖上印记
around the circle like that
像这样绕着圆圈转
and that should do it for today's
今天的情况应该就是这样
tutorial that is how you can go about
教程，这就是你可以如何去做
duplicating objects around a circle
复制圆形周围的对象
using inkscape
使用Inkscape
if you have any questions let me know
如果你有任何问题，请告诉我
and as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]